(Raj:)What did you put
for your best feature?
(Raj:)My parents' money.
(Raj:)What did you put
for your best feature?
I put "not applicable?
(Raj:)Come on, dude,
you're being too hard on yourself.
(Raj:)You've got a lot of good stuff
going on.
(Stuart:)Really? Like what?
Well, okay, you're a talented artist.
You own your own business.
(Stuart:)Neither of those things have
ever helped me meet a woman.
(Raj:)Okay, well, can we imply
that you're well-endowed?
(Stuart:)I do have one oddly long testicle.
(Raj:)Okay, now you're talking like
a winner!
What you doing?
(Sheldon:)Oh, it turns out Amy's beloved
Pride and Prejudice
(Sheldon:)is a flawless masterpiece.
(Sheldon:)He's got too much pride,
(Sheldon:)she's got too much prejudice--
it just works.
(Leonard:)So you're looking to ruin something
for her in the funny pages?